In this video, we're gonna continue our development of Cool type checking with a
在这段视频中，我们将继续开发Cool类型检查
discussion of type environments. Let's begin by doing some more type rules. So
关于文字环境的讨论。让我们从更多的类型规则开始。所以
here's one for the constant false. So it's provable that the constant false has the
这里有一个是针对常量False的。所以可以证明常量False具有
type [inaudible] and that's not surprising. If I have a string literal S,
输入[听不见]，这并不令人惊讶。如果我有一个字符串文字S，
then it's provable that, that has type string. And that's also not very
那么这是可以证明的，它有字符串类型。而且那也不是很
surprising. The expression new T produces an object of type T. And the type rule for
令人惊讶。表达式new T生成类型T的对象，类型规则为
that is very straightforward. New T has type T. And we're just going to ignore
这是非常直截了当的。新T的类型是T，我们只是打算忽略
self type for now. As I mentioned in an earlier video, we'll deal with self type
暂时自己打字。正如我在前面的视频中提到的，我们将处理Self类型
later in a video all on its own. Here are a couple of more rules. If it's provable
稍后在一段视频中，这一切都是单独进行的。这里有几条更多的规则。如果这是可以证明的
that an expression e has type bool then an e Boolean complement of e not e also has
表达式e具有bool类型，则e的e布尔补也具有
type bool. And finally perhaps our most complex rule so far, the rule for a while
键入bool。最后可能是我们目前为止最复杂的规则，暂时的规则
loop, and we call that the e-1 here is the predicate of the loop, this is what
循环，我们称这里的e-1为循环的谓词，这就是
determines if we keep executing the loop or not, and e2 is the body of the loop.
确定是否继续执行循环，e2是循环体。
And so type one is required to have type bool. It needs to be provable that e one
所以类型1需要有类型bool。它需要是可证明的，那就是
had type bool, and we allow e two, the body of the loop, to have an arbitrary
类型为bool，我们允许循环体e 2具有任意
type. It can have any type t. It has to have some type, so it has to be type able
键入。它可以有任何类型t。它必须有某种类型，所以它必须是可类型的
under some. Rules, but we don't care what the type is because the type of the entire
在一些下面。规则，但是我们不关心类型是什么，因为整个
expression is just object. We don't actually return the, this expression
表达式只是对象。我们实际上并没有返回这个表达式
doesn't return an interesting value, doesn't produce an interesting value, and
不返回感兴趣的值，不产生感兴趣的值，并且
to discourage people from trying to rely on it, we just type the whole thing as
为了不鼓励人们尝试依赖它，我们只需将整个代码键入为
object. And this is a little bit of a design decision. Now we could have
对象。这有点像是一个设计决定。现在我们可以
designed a language, for example, where the type of a while loop is, was type t.
例如，设计了一种语言，其中WHILE循环的类型是t。
And that you would get the last value of the loop that was that was executed but
并且您将获得执行的循环的最后一个值，但是
the problems is that if E one the protocol loop is false and reaches the loop the
问题是，如果E为1，则协议环路为假，并到达环路
first time Then you never evaluate e two, and no value is produced, and in that case
第一次，你永远不会计算e 2，也不会产生任何值，在这种情况下
you would get a, a void value. Which if so mebody tried to dereference, it would
你会得到一个，一个无效值。如果是这样的话我想取消引用，它会
result in a run time error. That's so to discourage programmers from lying On the
导致运行时错误。这样做是为了阻止程序员躺在
loop, producing a meaningful value. We could just type it, as object. So far,
循环，生成有意义的值。我们可以直接把它打成宾语。到目前为止,
it's been pretty straight forward to define reasonable type rules for every
为每个对象定义合理的类型规则非常简单
construct that we've looked at. But now we actually come to a problem. Let's say we
我们已经看过的结构。但现在我们实际上遇到了一个问题。比方说我们
have an expression which consists just of a single variable name, and that's a
我有一个表达式，它只由一个变量名组成，这是一个
perfectly valid, cool expression, and the question is, what is the type of that
非常有效，很酷的表达，问题是，这是什么类型的
variable, call it X And as you can see. When we're just looking at X by itself we
变量，将其命名为X，如您所见。当我们只看X本身的时候，我们
don't have enough information to give X a type. This local structural rule does not
没有足够的信息为X指定类型。此本地结构规则不
carry any information about the type of X And stepping back one level, inference
携带有关X类型的任何信息，并后退一级，推断
rules have the property that all the information needs to be local. Everything
规则的属性是所有信息都需要是本地的。所有的一切
we need to know. To carry out the function of the rule has to be present in the rule
我们需要知道。执行规则的功能必须出现在规则中
itself. There are no external data structures. There's nothing we're passing
它本身。没有外部数据结构。我们没有路过任何东西
around here that's on the side. Everything has to be encoded in this rule and, so far
在这附近，那个在边上。所有内容都必须按照此规则进行编码，到目前为止
at least, we just don't know Enough to say what the type of a variable should be. So
至少，我们知道的还不够多，不知道变量的类型应该是什么。所以
the solution to this problem is just to put more information in the rules, and
这个问题的解决方案就是在规则中加入更多的信息，并且
that's what we're going to do, so a type environment gives types for free
这就是我们要做的，所以类型环境免费提供类型
variables. So what is a free variable, a variable is free in an expression if it is
变量。那么，什么是自由变量，如果一个变量在表达式中是自由的，那么它就是自由的
not defined within that expression. So for example, in the expression X, X is free.
未在该表达式中定义。例如，在表达式X中，X是自由的。
In the expression x plus y (x+y), well, here this expression uses both x and y,
在表达式x+y(x+y)中，这里这个表达式既使用x又使用y，
and there's no definition of either x or y in that expression, so x and y are free
在这个表达式中没有x或y的定义，所以x和y是自由的
And that expression. If I have, let Y... So I'm declaring a variable Y in X + Y.
还有那个表情。如果我有，让你..。所以我在X+Y中声明一个变量。
Well what's free in this expression, well this expression uses X and Y but the use
这个表达式的自由之处在于，这个表达式使用了X和Y，但是使用
of Y is governed by a definition of Y that occurs within the expression itself. So we
OF Y由表达式本身内出现的Y定义控制。所以我们
say here that Y is bound, Y is a bound variable in this expression but X is still
这里假设Y是绑定的，Y是此表达式中的绑定变量，但X仍然是
free, so only X is free in that expression. And the ide a here is, that if
自由，所以在该表达式中只有X是自由的。这里的问题是，如果
I have an expression with three variables, and you want me to type check it, you have
我有一个有三个变量的表达式，您想让我键入check it，您需要
to tell me what the types of those variables are. So I can type check X if
告诉我这些变量的类型。这样我就可以输入check X if
you tell me what the type of X is. I can type check X plus Y if you tell me the
你告诉我X是什么类型的。我可以输入Check X加Y，如果你告诉我
types of X and Y. And I can type check this expression, this line expression, if
X和Y的类型，我可以键入Check这个表达式，这行表达式，如果
you tell me the type of its one free variable X, the type of Y. We will be
你告诉我它的一个自由变量X的类型，Y的类型。我们将成为
given a declaration by the let, but we still have to tell me what the type X is.
给出了LET的声明，但我们还是要告诉我X类型是什么。
So the free variables are just those variables where you have to give me the
所以自由变量就是那些你必须给我
information and then I can carry out the type checking. The type environment
信息，然后我就可以进行类型检查。类型环境
encodes this information so a type environment is a function from object
对此信息进行编码，以便类型环境是Object的函数
identifiers from variable names to types So let O be a type environment. One of
标识符从变量名到类型，所以让O表示类型环境。其中之一
these functions from object identifier names types. And now we're going to extend
这些函数来自对象标识符名称类型。现在我们要把
the kinds of logical statements that we prove to look like this. And the way that
我们证明的各种逻辑陈述看起来是这样的。而通过这种方式
this going to be read is that under the assumptions that variables have the types
我们要理解的是，在假设变量具有以下类型的情况下
given by O. So the assumptions go over here on the left side of the turnstile.
O给出的，所以假设在旋转栅门的左边。
These are the assumptions that we're making about the free variables in E. So
这些是我们对E.so中的自由变量所做的假设
the assumption that, excuse me, three variables. Have the types given by o is
打扰一下，假设有三个变量。具有由o给出的类型是
provable, that's this turn style here, that the expression e has type t. And, so
可以证明，这就是这里的转弯风格，表达式e的类型是t，所以
this notation very nicely, separates what we're assuming. This is input to our,
这个符号很好地分隔了我们的假设。这是对我们的投入，
process of figuring out what the type is from what we're proving. So if you tell me
从我们正在证明的东西中找出类型的过程。所以如果你告诉我
the types of the free variables as given by o, then I can tell you, the type e. The
o给出的自由变量的类型，那么我可以告诉你，e类型。
type environment has to be added to all the rules that we've gone through so far.
到目前为止，我们已经讨论过的所有规则中都必须添加类型环境。
So for example, for intergal literals if I have some set of assumptions of all the
例如，对于整数字面，如果我有一组假设
types of variables, that doesn't really change, it doesn't, in fact it doesn't
变量的类型，这不会真的改变，不会，事实上不会
change, what the type is an intergal literal. Any intergal literal will still
变，什么类型是整数文字。任何整数字面都不会改变
have type int. And so in this case, for this particular kind of expression, I we
具有类型int。所以在这种情况下，对于这种特殊的表达，我我们
don't use any of our assumptio ns about the types of variables. Now, it's a little
不要使用我们关于变量类型的任何假设。现在，这有点
bit different with the case of sum expressions. So if I have the expression E
与SUM表达式的情况略有不同。所以如果我有表达式E
one plus E two, and I have some assumptions, zero, about the types of
一加E2，我有一些假设，零，关于这些类型
variables, well, then I want to prove that E one has type int, and I'm gonna do that
变量，然后我想证明E 1有int类型，我会这么做
using the types of the variables given by zero, so E one might contain free
使用由零给出的变量类型，因此E 1可能包含FREE
variables and I'll need to look in zero to figure out what the types of those
变量，我需要在零中查找，才能找出这些变量的类型
variables are. And similarly for E two, I will type E two under the same set of
变量是。类似地，对于E 2，我将在相同的集合下键入E 2
assumptions. And if E1 has type int under the assumptions O and E2 has type int
假设。如果在假设下E1具有INT类型，则O和E2具有INT类型
under the assumptions O. Well, then I can conclude that E1 plus E2 has type int
在假设0的情况下，那么我可以得出结论，E1加E2的类型是int
under the same set of assumptions O. And we can also write new rules, so now our
在同样的假设下，我们也可以写出新的规则，所以现在我们
big problem with free variables becomes a very easy problem. If I want to know what
自由变量的大问题变成了一个非常简单的问题。如果我想知道
the type of X is, and there's a missing O here, if I want to know what the type of X
X的类型是，这里有一个漏掉的O，如果我想知道X的类型是什么
is, I simply look it up in my object environment. So under the assumption that
就是，我只需在我的对象环境中查找它。所以在假设
the variables have the types given by O, what is the type of x? Well, I look up in
变量有O给出的类型，x的类型是什么？嗯，我抬头看
O what the type of X is assumed to be, and I then can prove that X has that type T.
假设X的类型是什么，然后我就可以证明X有这个类型。
So now let's take a look at a rule that actually does something interesting with
现在让我们来看一条规则，它实际上做了一些有趣的事情
the variables from the point of view of the environments. So here is a [inaudible]
从环境的角度来看的变量。所以这里是[听不见的]
expression. And let's remind ourselves what this does. This is a [inaudible]
表达式。让我们提醒自己这是做什么用的。这是[听不见]
expression that has no initialization. So it says that X is going to be a new
没有初始化的表达式。所以它说X将是一个新的
variable. It's going to have type T0, and that variable is going to be visible in
变量。它将具有类型T0，该变量将在
the sub expression E1. And so, now, how am I going to type check that? Well, I'm
子表达式E1。那么，现在，我要如何输入检查呢？嗯，我是
going to type check E1 in some kind of environment. And this is a new notation
要在某种环境中键入check E1。这是一种新的记号
here, so let me define what it means. So remember O is a function, it maps a,
在这里，让我来定义一下它的意思。记住O是一个函数，它映射a，
variable names to types and OT/X this notation here is also a function. And what
类型和OT/X的变量名这里的符号也是一个函数。还有什么
this is, is the function O modified at the single point X to return T. So in
这就是，函数O在单点X处被修改为返回T。所以在
particular a, this function, this whole thing here is one function, this wh ole
特别是一个，这个功能，这里的整个就是一个功能，这个
thing I'm underlining here is a function, that applied to X is Returns t So that
我在这里下划线的是一个应用于X的函数，它返回t，因此
says that this sort of assumptions says that x has type t and for any other
表示这种假设表示x具有类型t，而对于任何其他类型
variable. So I apply it to some other variable y, where x is different from y.
变量。所以我把它应用于其他一些变量，其中x不同于y。
Well then, I just get whatever type y has in [inaudible]. Okay? So what this rule
好吧，那么，我只得到[听不见]中的任何一种类型的y。好吧?那么这条规则是什么呢？
then says is that I'm going to type check E1 in the same environment O, except that
然后说我将在相同的环境O中键入check E1，除了
at point X, it's going to have the type T0. So we're gonna change just the type of
在点X，它的类型是T0。所以我们要改变的只是一种
X that have type T0, because that's the type of the new identifier that's bound at
类型为T0的X，因为这是绑定在的新标识符的类型
E1. And all the other types will be the same. And using those assumptions, I'll
E1。而所有其他类型都将是相同的。利用这些假设，我将
try to prove that E1 has some type. I will get a type for E1. And then that will be
试着证明E1有某种类型。我去买个E1的型号。然后就会是
the type of the entire let expression. Now notice something about the type
整个let表达式的类型。现在请注意有关该类型的一些信息
environment. What this says is that before we type check E1, we need to modify Our
环境。这就是说，在我们键入check E1之前，我们需要修改我们的
set of assumption. Modify our type environment to include a new assumption
一组假设。修改我们的类型环境以包含新的假设
about x, then we type check e one, and then of course when we leave, type
关于x，然后我们键入check e one，当然，当我们离开时，键入
checking e one, we're going to remove that assumption about x, that new assumption,
检查一下e，我们要去掉关于x的那个假设，这个新的假设，
because outside of the let, we just have the original set of assumptions, though.
因为在LET之外，我们只有一组原始的假设。
And so, I hope that, that, terminology and that description reminds you of something
所以，我希望，术语和描述会让你想起一些事情
that we talked about earlier, because this type environment is really implemented by
这一点，因为这个类型环境实际上是由
the simple table. So, in our rules, The type environment that carries around the
简单的桌子。因此，在我们的规则中，携带
information that will be stored or is typically stored in the symbol table of a
将存储或通常存储在的符号表中的信息
compiler.
编译器。